THE
WORLD THESE
WISE
WORDS
WERE
SPOKEN
BY MAHATMA
GANDHI
A MAN
WHO
LED
WITH
PEACE AND
ENCOURAGED US
TO
BE THE
VERY BEST
VERSIONS
OF OURSELVES
BUT WHAT
DOES
IT
MEAN
WELL IMAGINE
YOU
HAVE A
TOY BOX
FILLED
WITH
ALL SORTS
OF
TOYS
BUT
EVERY
TIME YOU
WALK
BY
YOU
SEE
IT'S
MESSY WITH
TOYS EVERYWHERE
NOW YOU
WISH
IT WAS
TIDY RIGHT
GANDHI IS
SAYING
INSTEAD
OF
JUST WISHING
YOU SHOULD
START TIDYING
IT UP
YOURSELF BY
DOING SO
YOU'RE
ACTUALLY CREATING
THE
CHANGE
YOU WANT
TO
SEE
A
CLEAN
TOY
BOX IT'S
JUST
LIKE THAT
WITH
THE
WORLD IF
YOU
WANT MORE
KINDNESS START
BY
BEING KIND
IF
YOU WISH
FOR
MORE LAUGHTER
CRACK
A JOKE
AND SPREAD
SOME JOY
IT'S
ABOUT
TAKING
ACTION YOURSELF
NOT
WAITING
FOR
SOMEONE
ELSE
TO
MAKE THINGS
BETTER
SO
REMEMBER YOU
HAVE THE
POWER
TO MAKE
A
DIFFERENCE EVEN
WITH THE
SMALLEST ACTS
OF
KINDNESS
NOW
BEFORE
YOU
GO OUT
AND BE
A
SUPERHERO OF
CHANGE
DON'T
FORGET
IF
YOU ENJOYED
THIS
LITTLE
NUGGET OF
WISDOM
SMASH THAT
LIKE BUTTON
AND
HIT SUBSCRIBE
FOR MORE
INSPIRING SHORTS
TOGETHER LET'S
CREATE
A WAVE
OF POSITIVE
CHANGE
ONE CLICK
AT
A
TIME